My name is Chef Q-
Chef Q
... from Cooking With What You Got. Follow me on YouTube.
I'm here to tell you about Phil's Collision Center.
I'm going to tell you one thing, we met by accident, but it's no accident
that every time somebody need a little something, something done.
If it's a scratch, they got the paint to match, baby.
If it's a ding, it ain't no thing, baby.
If it's a crash, they going to smash that junk and get it back to the
point to where you love it, guaranteed.
I've had four vehicles in here. I hated it, but I loved
it because I knew for a fact. Phil's Collision, man, my boys
Eddie and Eddie, that's Big Eddie and Little Eddie.
All I knew was anytime anything happened, I brought it
straight here. If it's a fender bender or a total
crash out, Phil Collision is the place to be.
That's all I'm saying. They only got one location, so you bring your a*s down
here.